Noell James

Business Analyst

Deloitte Consulting USI [2018-Present]

An experienced software developer with 4 years of expertise in an Agile development. A logical and creative thinker who enjoys learning new languages, frameworks and technologies in general. Having strong problem solving and analytical skills

noelljames@gmail.com

+91 9605436386

Bangalore, India



WORK EXPERIENCE Sales force Integration

07/2020 - Present,

Santander -

 Integrated Salesforce platforms with existing Medallia instances which enabled automatically gathering customer feedback with a single trigger using Salesforce accounts.

Aetna –

 Integrated customer feedback from Medallia directly into Salesforce and allowing it to gather feedback on its own, thus providing the team with all the customer data it needs in one dashboard.

Operational Customer Experience Manager

10/2019 - Present,

Aetna –

- Implemented 'Text Analysis' to create structured data out of free text content which results in slicing & dicing heaps of unstructured documents into easy-to-manage & interpret data pieces
- Developed auto data population in surveys which helped reduce user efforts & improved data precision.

T-Mobile:

- Co-led the project to generate consumer satisfaction surveys that brought in much more targeted insights on service quality, CX & product attributes from the right customer.
- Transition to recently introduced Next Generation Reporting Feature producing more reactive, intuitive, consistent & provides reports with a better context.

Vodafone:

- Led the QA planning process end-to-end to achieve accurate & bug-free solution.
- Proactively addressed issues in ticketing configuration ensuring timely Go-Live.

Hybris Developer

04/2018 - 06/2019,

Carnival Cruise Line –

- Contributed as a Hybris developer to improve code coverage using Junit.
- As an offshore lead, I designed a solution for enhancing the onboarding experience for their interview candidates

SKILLS

Business Analysis

Analytics

Leadership

ACHIEVEMENTS

Won Applause Award for performance in Carnival Project.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Medallia
- Qualtrics

LANGUAGES

- Javascript
- JSON
- HTML
- Hybris

INTERESTS

Photography

Dance

Travelling

EDUCATION

MCA – Master of Computer Applications IGNOU

07/2021 - Present,

B.Sc – Computer Science YIMS College

07/2014 - 05/2017,